<modDesc descVersion="64">
    <author>Edge Gaming</author>
    <translationsby>Castiga</translationsby>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
	<title><!-- en=English de=German fr=French es=Spanish ru=Russian pl=Polish it=Italian br=Brazilian-Portuguese cs=Chinese(Simplified) ct=Chinese(Traditional) cz=Czech nl=Netherlands hu=Hungary jp=Japanese kr=Korean pt=Portuguese ro=Romanian tr=Turkish -->
        <en>Krampe Turbo Tracker</en>
        <de>Krampe Turbo Tracker</de>
        <fr>Krampe Turbo Tracker</fr>
        <es>Krampe Turbo Tracker</es>
        <ru>Krampe Турбо Трекер</ru>
        <pl>Krampe Turbo Tracker</pl>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Krampe Turbo Tracker is a great dolly for all your Farm work. It's got a long base and an adjustable trailer hitch, that you can move on the go. So if you ever in need of making a road train,
You will have enough room between the trailers.
It comes with TONS of costumization possibilities & alot Wheel Configurations, as well as Fully Costumizable Paint! Get that farm color on your dolly to!

Good luck with all your farming.

Below you will find detailed Description:

--Technical Info--
Krampe Turbo Tracker:
Price: 12.900€
Size: 3.5 x 6 Meters.
Weight: 2899kg
Recommended Power: 50 hp+
Attacher Joints: Trailer hitch.

-If you find any bugs or got suggestions for improvment, please dont hesitate to contact us on our Github page at https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
or Contact EDGEPureGaming on facebook.]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[Krampe Turbo Tracker ist ein großartiger Dolly für all Ihre Farmarbeiten. Es hat eine lange Basis und eine verstellbare Anhängerkupplung, die Sie unterwegs bewegen können. Wenn Sie also jemals einen Straßenzug brauchen,
Sie haben genug Platz zwischen den Anhängern.
Es kommt mit Tonnen von Kostümierungsmöglichkeiten und vielen Radkonfigurationen sowie vollständig kostümierbarer Farbe! Holen Sie sich diese Farmfarbe auf Ihren Dolly!

Viel Glück bei all deiner Landwirtschaft.

Nachfolgend finden Sie eine detaillierte Beschreibung:

--Technische Information--
Krampe Turbo Tracker:
Preis: 12.900 €
Größe: 3,5 x 6 Meter.
Gewicht: 2899 kg
Empfohlene Leistung: 50 PS +
Attacher-Gelenke: Anhängerkupplung.

-Wenn Sie Fehler finden oder Verbesserungsvorschläge haben, zögern Sie bitte nicht, uns auf unserer Github-Seite unter https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
zu kontaktieren oder EDGEPureGaming auf Facebook zu kontaktieren.]]></de>
        <fr><![CDATA[Krampe Turbo Tracker est un excellent chariot pour tous vos travaux agricoles. Il a une longue base et un attelage de remorque réglable, que vous pouvez déplacer en déplacement. Donc, si jamais vous avez besoin de faire un train routier,
Vous aurez suffisamment d'espace entre les remorques.
Il est livré avec des tonnes de possibilités de personnalisation et de nombreuses configurations de roues, ainsi que de la peinture entièrement personnalisable! Obtenez cette couleur de ferme sur votre chariot!

Bonne chance avec toute votre agriculture.

Ci-dessous, vous trouverez une description détaillée:

--Info technique--
Krampe Turbo Tracker:
Prix: 12.900 €
Taille: 3,5 x 6 mètres.
Poids: 2899 kg
Puissance recommandée: 50 ch +
Attacher Joints: Attelage de remorque.

-Si vous trouvez des bugs ou avez des suggestions d'amélioration, n'hésitez pas à nous contacter sur notre page Github à https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
ou Contacter EDGEPureGaming sur facebook.]]></fr>
        <es><![CDATA[Krampe Turbo Tracker es una gran plataforma para todo el trabajo de tu granja. Tiene una base larga y un enganche de remolque ajustable, que puede mover sobre la marcha. Entonces, si alguna vez necesitas hacer un tren de carretera,
Tendrás suficiente espacio entre los trailers.
¡Viene con TONELADAS de posibilidades de personalización y muchas configuraciones de ruedas, así como pintura totalmente personalizable! ¡Consigue ese color de granja en tu carro!

Buena suerte con toda tu agricultura.

A continuación encontrará una descripción detallada:

--Información técnica--
Krampe Turbo Tracker:
Precio: 12.900 €
Tamaño: 3.5 x 6 metros.
Peso: 2899kg
Potencia recomendada: 50 hp +
Attacher Joints: enganche de remolque.

-Si encuentra algún error u obtiene sugerencias de mejora, no dude en contactarnos en nuestra página de Github en https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
o póngase en contacto con EDGEPureGaming en Facebook.]]></es>
        <ru><![CDATA[Krampe Турбо трекер - отличная тележка для всей вашей фермерской работы. У него длинная база и регулируемое прицепное устройство, которое можно перемещать на ходу. Так что, если вам когда-нибудь понадобится сделать автопоезд,
У вас будет достаточно места между трейлерами.
Он поставляется с ДЕСЯТИМИ вариантами костюмизации и множеством конфигураций колес, а также полностью окрашиваемой краской! Получи этот цвет фермы на твоей тележке!

Удачи со всем вашим хозяйством.

Ниже вы найдете подробное описание:

--Техническая информация--
Крампе Турбо трекер:
Цена: 12,900 €
Размер: 3,5 х 6 метров.
Вес: 2899 кг
Рекомендуемая мощность: 50 л.с. +
Присоединение Присоединения: сцепка Трейлера.

-Если вы обнаружите какие-либо ошибки или получите предложения по улучшению, пожалуйста, не стесняйтесь связаться с нами на нашей странице Github по адресу https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
или связаться с EDGEPureGaming на Facebook.]]></ru>
        <pl><![CDATA[Krampe Turbo Tracker to świetny wózek do wszystkich prac na farmie. Ma długą podstawę i regulowany zaczep do przyczepy, dzięki czemu możesz poruszać się w dowolnym miejscu. Jeśli więc kiedykolwiek potrzebujesz pociągu drogowego,
Będziesz miał wystarczająco dużo miejsca między przyczepami.
Pochodzi z mnóstwem możliwości kostiumizacji i wielu konfiguracji kół, a także w pełni modyfikowalną farbą! Zdobądź ten kolor farmy na wózku!

Życzymy powodzenia w prowadzeniu gospodarstwa.

Poniżej znajdziesz szczegółowy opis:

--Informacje techniczne--
Krampe Turbo Tracker:
Cena: 12.900 €
Rozmiar: 3,5 x 6 metrów.
Waga: 2899 kg
Zalecana moc: 50 KM +
Łączniki do przyczep: Zaczep do przyczepy.

-Jeśli znajdziesz jakieś błędy lub masz sugestie dotyczące ulepszeń, nie wahaj się skontaktować z nami na naszej stronie Github pod adresem https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
lub Skontaktuj się z EDGEPureGaming na Facebooku.]]></pl>
        <it><![CDATA[Krampe Turbo Tracker è un carrello ideale per tutti i tuoi lavori agricoli. Ha una lunga base e un gancio di traino regolabile, che puoi spostare in movimento. Quindi, se mai hai bisogno di fare un treno stradale,
Avrai abbastanza spazio tra i rimorchi.
Viene fornito con tonnellate di possibilità di costumizzazione e molte configurazioni delle ruote, nonché vernice completamente personalizzabile! Ottieni quel colore di fattoria sul tuo carrello per!

Buona fortuna con tutta la tua agricoltura.

Di seguito troverai una descrizione dettagliata:

--Informazioni tecniche--
Krampe Turbo Tracker:
Prezzo: 12.900 €
Dimensioni: 3,5 x 6 metri.
Peso: 2899 kg
Potenza consigliata: 50 CV +
Giunti Attacher: gancio di traino.

-Se trovi qualche bug o hai suggerimenti per l'improvvisazione, non esitare a contattarci sulla nostra pagina Github all'indirizzo https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
o Contatta EDGEPureGaming su Facebook.]]></it>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>turboDolly_icon.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <storeItems>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="turboDolly.xml"/>
    </storeItems>
    <vehicleTypes>
        <type name="edge_Dolly" parent="trailer" filename="$dataS/scripts/vehicles/Vehicle.lua">
            <specialization name="motorized"/>
            <specialization name="enterable"/>
            <specialization name="drivable"/>
            <specialization name="honk"/>
        </type>
    </vehicleTypes>
    <l10n filenamePrefix="modDesc/modDesc_l10n"/>
    <credits><![CDATA[
## Translations
- Castiga
## Contributors
- EDGE Gaming, Castiga
## Designers
- Castiga, GIANTS Software]]></credits>
</modDesc>
